Check if only static GUI is shown
Text
Tick Time, test 0:00:00.00 format
Tick Time, test only number format
Text
Tick Time, test xms format
Tick Time, test xcs format
Text
Tick Time, test xs format
Tick Time, test xm format
Text
Tick Time, test xh format
Tick Time, test xf format
Text
Tick layer, test increasing layer
Tick layer, test decreasing layer with a value that makes it negative. The result should be zero.
Text
Test left, right and vertical margin with positive value
Test left, right and vertical margin with negative value such that the value will be negative. The result should be zero.
Text
With pos ticked,
Add 5, 0
Add 0, 5
Add -5, 0
Add 0,-5
Add 5,5
Add -5,5
Text
With pos ticked,
Add 5, 0
Add 0, 5
Add -5, 0
Add 0,-5
Add 5,5
Add -5,5
With fsc ticked,
Add 30
Add -30 and check if it changes in both fscx and fscy
Text
With fscx ticked,
Add 30
Add -30
Text
With fscy ticked,
Add 30
Add -30
Text
Taking turns with each color ticked, add 5,5,5 and check if r, g, b value increases by 5. Do the same for negative value
Give wrong input to color. Single color, text, 2 digit comma separated etc
Text
Add positive and negative value to borders. Try to make it negative as well.
Add +ve and -ve value in font spacing and size. Font spacing can be negative but size shouldn't be less than 1.
Text
Take turns with frx, fry, frz, fax, fay ticked, add positive and negative value
Add +ve and -ve values to alpha. Try to make it more than 255 or less than 0.
Text
With org ticked,
Add 5, 0
Add 0, 5
Add -5, 0
Add 0,-5
Add 5,5
Add -5,5
Text
Add +ve and -ve value for rectangular clip. Do the same for x1,y1 and x2,y2 only.
Add +ve and -ve time for both t1 and t2 at once and separately. Try to make it negative.
Text
Add +ve and -ve value for rectangular iclip. Do the same for x1,y1 and x2,y2 only.
Add +ve and -ve value for vectorial iclip. Do x and y separately and at once.
Text
Add +ve and -ve value for vectorial clip. Do x and y separately and at once.
Add +ve and -ve value for move x1, y1 only, x2, y2 only, t1, t2 or whole move.
Text
Add +ve and -ve value for variuos parameters of fade separated by comma
Add +ve and -ve value in centiseconds to change value of karaoke tags. Try to make it negative. Also try to increase by absurd amount.
BON VOYAGE! Hitokakera no yuuki hirogete
Add +ve and -ve value for x only, y only or both.
Transform
TEST
A long and winding road
Try to teleport. All pos, move and clip tags should move along with specified amount.
Text
Try increase with each line option
Increase with each line
Shift time but preserve time. The karaoke tag timing should not change even though start time or end time changes.
BON VOYAGE!Hitokakera no yuuki hirogete
Test
Shift time but preserve time. The fade in frame as well as fade out frame should not change.
Shift time but preserve time. The position and time due to move tag should not change.
Test