Check if all the tags present in the line are shown in script
Color
Border/Shadow
Font Size/Scale/Name
Perspective
Alpha
Align/Positon/Origin
Fade/Clip
Transform/Iclip
Move/Complex Fade
ibus
q/Vectorial Clip
blur/be/k
Text
Check if junk tags is picked up
and remove them
Check if unknown tags is picked up
Junk Tags
Unknown Tags
Check removing tags from the lines below using only "Remove Tags" button
Text
Check if tags are picked from inline tags
TEST
Start tag block is missing,
Start Tag should not be shown in the top Row
TEST
Inline tag block is missing,
InlineTag should not be shown in the top Row
Text
Transforms should not be shown in the top Row when transform is missing
Transform
No Transform
Tick Start Tag in top Row
Remove color using  "Remove Tags" button
It should only be removed from start tag block
A long and winding road
Tick Inline Tag in top Row
Remove color using  "Remove Tags" button
It should only be removed from inline tags block
A long and winding road
Tick Transform in top Row
Remove \fscx using  "Remove Tags" button
It should only be removed from inside the transform
A long and winding road
Tick Invert in top Row
Remove \fscx and \fs using  "Remove Tags" button
It should remove all tags except ticked ones
Text
Tick 'Invert' and 'Start Tags' in top Row
Remove \frz using  "Remove Tags" button
It should remove all tags except \frz but only in start tag
A long and winding road
Tick 'Invert' and 'Inline Tags' in top Row
Remove \frz using  "Remove Tags" button
It should remove all tags except \frz but only in inline tags
A long and winding road
Tick 'Invert' and 'Transform' in top Row
Remove \fscx using  "Remove Tags" button
It should remove all tags except \fscx but only in transform
A long and winding road
Press 'Remove All' Button
All tags should be removed
A long and winding road
Tick Start Tag in top Row
Press 'Remove All' Button
All start tags should be removed
A long and winding road
Tick 'Inline Tags' in top Row
Press 'Remove All' Button
All inline tags should be removed
A long and winding road
Only `Color` group should be visible in the left column
Only `Rotation` and `Perspective` group should be visible in the left column
A long and winding road
Only `Scale` group should be visible in the left column
Only `Remove all inline tags except last` group should be visible in the left column
A long and winding road
Tick the `Color` group in the left column
Press `Remove Group` button
Only the Color tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
Tick the `Rotation` group in the left column
Press `Remove Group` button
Only the Rotation tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
Tick the `Perspective` group in the left column
Press `Remove Group` button
Only the Perspective tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
Tick the `Scale` group in the left column
Press `Remove Group` button
Only the Scale tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
Tick the `Color` group in the left column and `Invert` in the top Row
Press `Remove Group` button
Everything except the Color tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
Tick the `Rotation` group in the left column and `Invert` in the top Row
Press `Remove Group` button
Everything except the Rotation tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
Tick the `Perspective` group in the left column and `Invert` in the top Row
Press `Remove Group` button
Everything except the Perspective tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
Tick the `Scale` group in the left column and `Invert` in the top Row
Press `Remove Group` button
Everything except the Scale tags should be removed from the line
A long and winding road
A line with no tags.
A dialog should pop up informing no tags in selected line
A long and winding road